website-hit-counters.com 2014-02-09

# Website Hit Counters, Privacy Policy

Website-hit-counters.com. collects basic information from you to support your experience on our site. Your privacy will be respected and you have our assurance that website-hit-counters.com maintains and uses any information collected responsibly.

**General Browsing:**

Website-hit-counters.com gathers navigational information about where you go on our web site. This allows us to see which pages are most visited. This helps website-hit-counters.com to improve the quality of visitors' online experience by recognizing and delivering more of the features, services and products our visitors prefer. Additional non-personally identifiable information (i.e. domain type, browser version, service provider and IP address) may be collected which will provide information regarding your use of our Web site (such as the time of your last visit to a page on our site).

**Disclosure of Personal Information:**

Any information you provide to us when you establish or update an account, purchase services online or request information (i.e. name, address, e-mail address, telephone number and credit card information), is maintained in private files on our secure Web servers and our internal systems. This information is used to enable Website-hit-counters.com to deliver services to you. To ensure compliance with federal law, Website-hit-counters.com does not maintain information provided by children under the age of 18 and you must be 18 years of age to open an account.

When required by law, or based on our good faith belief that conformity to the law or compliance with regulations requires that we disclose specific information about you, we will disclose only the minimum information required by law to appropriate law enforcement agencies.

Website-hit-counters.com does not sell, rent or trade your e-mail address to third parties. We do not use third parties to fulfill any of our services.

**Email and Communication Policy:**

Website-hit-counters.com gathers your email address when you (a) sign up for one of our hit counters or (b) when you send us an email.

We do not add email addresses to our database when the email address is not associated with an existing customer, or unless the individual explicitly requests to be added to our database.

By signing up for an account, you grant us permission to contact you regarding details of your transaction, provide product service announcements and upgrade information, or provide other information necessary to maintain your account or conduct the services you have ordered.

All new customers receive a confirmation of account activity email. In this email you are given the opportunity to choose to receive newsletters, emails and other communication from our company. All emails from website-hit-counters.com will contain a link to have your email address removed from our database and we honor any and all requests or changes to your preferences about receipt of communication from us.

**Use of Cookies:**

Website-hit-counters.com uses a browser feature known as a cookie, which assigns a unique identification to your computer. Cookies also allow Website-hit-counters.com to make our sites more responsive to your needs by delivering a better and more personalized experience to you. The cookies are typically stored on your computer's hard drive and are used by Website-hit-counters.com to help track your clicks as you go through the pages within Website-hit-counters.com. In addition, Website-hit-counters.com uses cookies to help keep track of support requests and to tell us whether you have previously visited Website-hit-counters.com. This allows registered users to avoid reentering information upon every new visit to our site.

**Updating Personal Information:**

We strive to ensure that your personal information is accurate and up-to-date. To do this, we provide you with the opportunity to update or modify your personal information by logging into your account. You may also modify your email and communication preferences at any time.

**Links:**

For your convenience, our Web site may contain links to other sites. Website-hit-counters.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Questions/Changes in Policy:**

If you have questions or concerns with respect to our Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us.

**You may also contact us by mail at the following address:**

Website-hit-counters.com  
3305 W. Mayflower Ave, Suite #3  
Lehi, Utah 84043  
United States

You may contact us by e-mail at webmaster@website-hit-counters.com or by calling 801.768.9419 x 22

If elements of our Privacy Policy change, we will post the policy changes in our Privacy Policy on this Web site. If you are concerned about how your personal information is used, please visit our site often for this and other important announcements about Website-hit-counters.com.
